<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!--    Categories names-->
    <string name="food_category">Food</string>
    <string name="place_category">Place</string>
    <string name="shopping_category">Shopping</string>
    <string name="restaurant_category">Restaurant</string>

    <!--    Address of the places mentioned-->
    <string name="dutch_garden">Dutch Garden Road,\nNanpura\nSurat, Gujarat</string>
    <string name="dumas_beach">Dumas Road, \nSurat, Gujarat</string>
    <string name="khudawand_khan">"Sayedpura \nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="iskcon_temple">"Ashram Rd,\nJahangir Pura,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="suvali_beach">"Suvali Beach Road,\nHazira,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="surat_castle">"Near dakka ovara,\nmakkai pull,\nChowk Bazar,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden">"Ugat,\nBhesan Rd,\nJahangirabad,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>

    <string name="vr_mall">"Dumas Rd,\nMagdalla,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="rahul_raj">"Dumas Road,\nPiplod,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="iscon_mall">"Opposite Rajhans Theater,\nPiplod,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="central_mall">"Opposite Valentine Multiplex,\nDumas Road,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>

    <string name="sasumaa">"Mangal Deep Complex,\nOpp. Vanita Vishram Ground,\nMajura Gate,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="sai_dosa">Opp. Valentine,\nDumas Road,\nSurat, Gujarat</string>
    <string name="mysore_cafe">"Daruwalla Building Besides Athwa Petrol Pump,\nAthwalines,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>
    <string name="only_dhosa">"Avalon The Commercial Hub Nr. Samast Patidar Samaj's Wadi,\n" + "Katargam,\nSurat, <Gujarat></Gujarat>"</string>
    <string name="ramji">"12/3173, 3174, Kaskiwadi Baghal Road,\nBhagal Char Rasta,\nSurat, Gujarat"</string>

    <!--Info of the places-->
    <string name="dutuch_garden_inf">Dutch Garden is located in Nanpura and is one of the most popular tourist sites in Surat.
        Besides beauty, the garden has got a lot of history behind it to fascinate as well as refresh the busy city souls. The garden
        has been designed in a European style. The well-planned and well-maintained garden gives a wonderful recreational space to the
        locals as well as tourists. People use it for morning and evening walks, and to have get togethers or to enjoy a quiet time alone
        with oneself in the serenity of the atmosphere. River Tapi flowing at one side of the park adds immensely to the beauty of the park
        and helps the visitors unwind and feel good.\n\n

        The Dutch Garden is also the resting place of certain English and Dutch explorers who landed and settled in Surat. The most remarkable
        mausoleum is that of Baron Adrian Van Reed. He was the person who is believed to have established the first Dutch port for trading in
        Surat: Reed died in 1691. The interesting thing is that these impressive burial sites also enhance the beauty and brilliance of the place.</string>


    <string name="dumas_beach_inf">Along the Arabian Sea and about 13 miles southwest of Surat, nestled in the Western Indian state of Gujarat,
        lies the Dumas Beach. Unequivocally, it is one of the most beautiful and scenic beaches, but amidst all the beauty lies a paranormal
        mystery, which awaits to be discovered.\n\n
        While this seemingly mysterious beach in the South Gujarat is notorious for its paranormal activity, another thing it’s famous for is
        its black sand. According to folklore, the beach was used as a burial ground for Hindus and because of the remains of the people
        supposedly buried here, it is said to result in black sand. Furthermore, some say that the departed souls of the evil spirits roam the
        beach at midnight, which attributed to the formation of black sand and made it a haunted spot.</string>

    <string name="khudawand_khan_inf">The Tomb of Khudawand Khan is located near the Chakla Bazaar. The tomb was built on the honour of
        Khudawand Khan, a former Governor of Surat. The tomb is beautiful and is made using Islamic caricature and architecture. There is a
        plaque with information about the life of Khudawand Khan near the tomb.</string>

    <string name="iskcon_temple_inf">The Vedic scriptures state that spiritual life begins when one inquires into the nature of the absolute
        truth, the Supreme Godhead. Gaudiya Vaisnavas are monotheists and know the personality of Godhead as Krishna, the All-attractive. But
        it is also recognised that the Supreme has unlimited names such as Rama, Buddha, Vishnu, Jehovah, Allah, etc. The ultimate goal of
        Gaudiya Vaisnavism is to develop a loving relationship with the Supreme Godhead. To understand knowledge of self-realisation one must
        approach a genuine spiritual masterThe Vedas also.</string>

    <string name="suvali_beach_inf">Suvali Beach, a calm and serene beach, is situated at a distance of 20 km from Surat. Mostly visited by
        solitude seekers, the beach is slowly developing into a tourist spot. Located away from the heart of the city, the pristine beach
        offers a perfect getaway for the city people and other tourists away from the screeching noise and the fast-moving life of the city.\n\n

        The beach is situated in a calm environment where one can quite distinctly identify the sound of the gentle waves wash up the shoreline.
        It is a black sand beach which goes on miles along. In addition to this, the texture of the sand is soft, and one can easily dig his/her
        feet and toes inside while standing or taking a stroll on the beach. Since there are not many people visiting the beach, you get to
        relax and experience solitude there. There are no vendors or restaurants situated near the beach thereby providing you with complete
        isolation.</string>

    <string name="surat_castle_inf">A historic fort, Surat Castle was built in the 18th century to safeguard the city from the Portuguese.
        Today, the fort stands tall on the bank of the Tapi River. Visit the fort if you love history and old architecture. While you are
        at the castle, enrol yourself for the video presentation, it takes you back in time and shows you the might of Gujarat’s Sultanate.</string>

    <string name="botanical_garden_inf">The Sneh Rashmi Botanical Garden in Surat is a popular hangout spot for locals. The parks is great place
        to visit to get away from the noise of city life. Surrounded by gorgeous trees, the garden is home to wide walking tracks, a pond and
        many exotic plants.\n\n

        There is plenty to do at the park, children can enjoy the mini train rides, and couples can spend quality time with each other, enjoying
        nature. Fitness enthusiasts can jog or take long walks on the pathways at the Sneh Rashmi Botanical Garden.</string>

    <!--    Food inf-->
    <string name="dabeli">It\'s like Vada Pav with a major twist!</string>
    <string name="fafda">The Dream Cheat Day Breakfast!</string>
    <string name="locho">The snack you couldn\'t say no to!</string>
    <string name="khaman">The Sponge Snack!</string>
    <string name="gota">The Gujarati Pakoras!</string>
    <string name="khandvi">Soft Layers</string>
    <string name="muthiya">The snack you couldn\'t say no to!</string>
</resources>